Sorry... I'm sure you're tired.
（里見(さとみ)蓮太郎(れんたろう)）悪い 疲れてるよな
It's all right.
（ティナ）大丈夫です
I've been thinking that I
should see Dr. Muroto soon.
遠からず ドクター室戸(むろと)には
会わなければならないと
思っていました
I heard that despite being a genius,
she is extremely strange.
なんでも 天才の例に漏れず
大変な変人だとか
That's putting it lightly...
そんな
なまやさしいもんじゃねえぞ
Huh?
えっ？
Sensei!
（蓮太郎）先生！
あ…
Hey, Sensei!
（蓮太郎）おーい 先生
Where'd she go...
どこ行ったんだよ？
ったく…
（室戸 菫(すみれ)）ハァ ハァ…
わあ～
（菫）ううっ あああ…
No!
（ティナ）イヤー！
♪～
～♪
You really saved me, Rentaro-kun.
#09 The Protectors of the Barrier
（菫）いやいや
助かったよ 蓮太郎くん
My food supply had run out
and I was about to die...
備品の食料が尽きていて
危うく死にかけた
But the sticky sweet fruit of dried
persimmons keeps stimulating
しかし 干し柿というのは
ドロドロの甘い果肉が
すきっ腹を刺激して非常に不快…
my empty stomach and it's rather unpleasant.
ん？
Rentaro-kun...
蓮太郎くん
This means you're gonna be
locked up for a long time.
これは 相当 長い間
ぶち込まれることになるぞ
I didn't kidnap her.
さらってきたんじゃねえよ
Onii-san wouldn't do something like that.
お兄さんは そんなことはしません
Well, well...
おやおや
He's felt the butts of a
hundred young girls in passing,
彼は すれ違いざまに
幼女の尻をなでること100回
and invaded elementary schools to
steal stool samples a thousand times.
小学校に侵入して
検便を盗むこと1000回
He is the grand master of all perverts.
変態グランドマスターだよ
I didn't know you were a
person of such stature.
そのような 大層なお方とは
つゆ知らず
I've been terribly rude to you...
今まで とんだご無礼をば…
Don't believe her!
（蓮太郎）信じるな！
By the way, just the day before yesterday,
そうだ　つい 一昨日
彰磨(しょうま)くんが君を訪ねてきたよ
Shoma-kun was looking for you.
あ… 彰磨兄(にい)が？
Shoma-nii was?
I said you weren't here at the moment,
（菫）今はいないと言ったら
話を聞かずに出ていってしまった
then he left without telling me anything.
He doesn't change, does he?
相変わらずだね 彼
Who's that?
誰ですか？
（蓮太郎）ああ 薙沢(なぎさわ)彰磨
Nagisawa Shoma.
He's a senior practitioner of
mine in the Tendo Martial Arts.
天童(てんどう)式戦闘術の 俺の兄弟子だ
He was so strong that I stood
no chance against him...
俺なんか足元にも及ばないくらい
強かった
But one day, he suddenly left the dojo.
でも ある日
突然 道場を辞めちまって
You respected him?
尊敬してたんですか？
Yeah...
そうだな
I was really sad when he left.
いなくなっちまって
すっげー悲しかった
I didn't get why he left without saying anything.
なんで 何も言わずに
行っちまったんだよってな
Doctor, I'd like to discuss something with you.
ドクター 相談があります
（菫）ん？
I will soon have people pursuing me.
私には 遠からず
追っ手がかかります
You mean Ayn?
エインのヤツか
When that happens, I will be
an inconvenience to everyone.
そうなったら
皆さんにも迷惑がかかります
Wouldn't it be better if I left
the Tendo Civil Security Agency?
私 やっぱり 天童民間警備会社を
出るべきじゃないでしょうか
You idiot!
How foolish.
（菫）バカだねえ
（蓮太郎）アホ！
Huh?
えっ？
Kisara-san, Enju and I aren't
木更(きさら)さんも延珠(えんじゅ)も俺も
お前に心配されるほど弱かねえよ！
so weak that you need to worry about us.
Tina-chan,
ティナちゃん
if I were to give a liberal translation
of what Rentaro-kun is trying to say...
蓮太郎くんの言いたいことを
意訳すると
It'd be: "You're a vital part of
my little girl harem plan,
お前は 幼女ハーレム計画の
貴重な１匹だから
so there's no way I'm letting you get away."
逃がすわけにはいかねえぜ
Or something like that...
とまあ こんなところだ
（ティナ）え…
She obviously made that up!
作り話に決まってんだろ！
Say, Tina.
なあ ティナ
You don't dislike us, right?
俺たちを嫌いなわけじゃないよな？
（ティナ）うん
Then there's no problem.
じゃあ 何も問題ねえだろ？
あっ
Don't worry. I'll become even stronger.
安心しろ
俺も もっと強くなるから
Thank you...
よろしくお願いします
She's a good kid.
いい子じゃないか
So how do you actually feel
about Enju-chan and Tina-chan?
実際のところ 君は 延珠ちゃんや
ティナちゃんのことを―
どう思ってるんだ？
Well, I think they're cute...
（蓮太郎）まあ かわいいと思うよ
The things they do without thinking
make my heart skip sometimes.
時々 何気ないしぐさに
ドキッとさせられる
Being so honest is a good thing. However...
素直でよろしい
でも あまり肩入れしすぎるな
Don't get too attached.
The Cursed Children are bound
by their body corrosion rate,
彼女たちには 体内侵食率という
逃れられない枷(かせ)がはまっている
a shackle they cannot escape.
They are different from us.
我々とは違うんだ
Enju is human just like you and me!
延珠は 俺ともあんたとも
変わらない人間だ！
But people who believe that are the minority.
（菫）だが
そう思っている人間は少数派だ
If you want to change our world,
こんな世界を変えたいと思うなら
君は 政治家になるべきだった
you should have become a politician.
There's more than one way
to change the world.
世界の変え方は
一とおりじゃないだろ
The freedom to see a bigger world
ガストレアに おびえなくてもいい
where we don't have to be
frightened by the Gastrea...
もっと広い世界を
見に行ける自由を―
I'd like to give that to Enju and Tina.
延珠や このティナに俺は与えたい
And for that, I'll defeat all of the Gastrea!
そのために倒す！
ガストレアを全部！
フッハハハハ…
なるほど そうきたか
I see. So that's your answer.
You truly are different from me.
やはり 君は 私とは違うね
Do you know what the most beautiful
thing in this universe is?
君 この宇宙で一番美しいものが
なんだか知ってるかい？
In Buddhism, apparently it's the
lotus flower... in other words,
仏教の世界ではね
蓮(はす)の花だそうだよ
you, since your name comes from that word.
つまり 君だ 蓮太郎くん
You have a beautiful soul.
君の魂は美しい
Seeing the way you are now,
今の君ならば
あれを見せても大丈夫だろう
I believe it'd be all right
to show you that thing.
This is the data I was able to get from
the Level Five access key you brought me.
君から預かった
レベル５のアクセスキーで―
引き出せたデータだ
あ… これは？
This is...
Kanto Battle
The Gastrea and JASDF...
A time line going back twenty
years from the present 2031.
（菫）2031年現在から
過去20年にわたって―
"Heaven's Ladder" Project
Secretly plotted by the government
"New Humanity Creation Plan"
さかのぼった年表だ
Take a look right here.
ここを見ろ
Gastrea War Outbreak
2021/xx/xx: Nanahoshi Village destroyed
Kanto Battle
The Gastrea and JASDF clash
（蓮太郎）あっ おかしい
Something's not right.
All records from the beginning
to the end of the Gastrea War
ガストレア戦争の
初期から末期にかけての記録は―
should have been destroyed.
焼失してるはずだ！
That's what the textbooks say, right?
教科書には そう書いてあるだろ？
だが…
However...
Gastrea War Outbreak
Your access key level is insufficient.
はっ
That's right. Someone is
concealing this information.
そう　ここは誰かが
そのこと自体を隠蔽しているんだ
Nanahoshi Village destroyed
Nanahoshi...
七星…
Inheritance of "Nanahoshi," the Seven Stars...
七星の遺産
（携帯電話の着信音）
Hello, Kisara-san?
（蓮太郎）もしもし 木更さん？
Satomi-kun. Are you watching the news?
（天童木更）
里見くん ニュース見てる？
The whitening of the Monolith
has been discovered.
モノリスの白化現象が発覚したわ！
Look at this! It's unbelievable!
（レポーター）
皆さん ご覧ください！
全く信じ難い惨状です！
The official announcement hasn't been made,
Monolith 32 is turning white
and beginning to collapse!
（木更）
公式発表は まだだけど―
第32号モノリスが―
but it looks like they couldn't hide it any longer.
もう 隠しきれなくなったみたい！
白く変色し
形状崩壊が始まりました
It's begun, Satomi-kun.
あっ モノリス周辺から
黒煙が立ち上って―
（木更）始まったわよ 里見くん
あっ モノリス周辺から
黒煙が立ち上って―
Yeah...
（蓮太郎）ああ
が… 外周区の外に…
Today, the day after the whitening
of Monolith 32 was reported,
（アナウンサー）
32号モノリスの白化現象を
確認してから―
一夜明けた今日
an official press conference
is being held by Seitenshi-sama.
聖居では 聖天子(せいてんし)様による
公式会見が開かれました
Including today, Monolith 32
（聖天子）
本日を１日目とカウントして
32号モノリスは
will most likely be destroyed in four days.
あと４日で崩壊すると見られます
（シャッター音）
What can you tell us about a
new Monolith being constructed?
（記者）
新しいモノリスの建設については
どのようになりますか？
Does this mean that you had prior
knowledge of this, Seitenshi-sama?
（記者）聖天子様は 今回のことを
事前に把握されていたと
いうことでしょうか？
Seitenshi-sama Emergency Press Conference
She's having to bear the full
brunt of it all... Poor thing.
（片桐(かたぎり)玉樹(たまき)）
矢面に立たされて―
気の毒にな
They say there are arguments
地下シェルターに入れる市民を
抽選でふるいにかけてるって政策も
for and against using a lottery
to screen candidates
for the underground shelter.
賛否両論みたいだ
Can't we have the other citizens
evacuate to other areas?
残りの市民は
ほかに避難させられないのか？
I heard the rich men have
already spent a lot
リッチメンたちは
すでに 大金積んで
of money buying up all the airline tickets.
航空券 買い占めてるって話だぜ
I'm sure it's only a matter of time
before everyone else starts rioting.
それ以外の連中が殺気だつのも
時間の問題だろ
Rentaro, it's finished!
（藍原(あいはら)延珠）蓮太郎 出来たぞ
Is this really a tent?
（片桐弓月(ゆづき)）
マジで これテントなの？
It's just rags!
雑巾じゃん
It can't be helped.
（蓮太郎）しょうがないだろ
If we're not officially
registered as an adjuvant,
正式にアジュバントとして
登録されてないと―
they won't give us a JASDF tent.
自衛隊のテントは
支給してもらえねえんだ
Just one more pair!
あと１組 なんとしても
今日中に見つけるよ！
We're going to find them
today, no matter what!
There's no way I can sleep in such
a cramped space with this pervert.
こんな変態と こんな狭いとこで
一緒に寝れないっての
（蓮太郎）ハァ…
I'm sorry... If only I could join you...
すみません
私も仲間に入れたらいいのですが
Don't worry about it.
Your rank's currently revoked.
気にすんな
お前は 序列剥奪中なんだから
Don't worry, Tina!
心配するな ティナ
I shall capture the most
amazing comrades for us!
妾(わらわ)が超すごい仲間を
つかまえてくる
It's not as fun as you're making it sound...
お前が思ってるほど
楽しい作業じゃないぞ
Then I shall make it fun!
じゃあ 妾が楽しくする！
（延珠）わあ～！
蓮太郎 早く早くー！
Rentaro! Hurry! Hurry!
There are so many people...
すっげー人だな
It's almost like a festival.
まるで お祭りみたいだな
A festival? Really?
お祭りって お前…
Oh! Rentaro, how about them?
あっ 蓮太郎
あんなのはどうだ？
No, let's skip them.
いや あいつらはやめておこう
見てみろ
Take a look.
He's armored from head to toe.
全身防具でびっしりだ
People do that when they don't want to die,
死にたくないって気持ちから
ああなりがちだが
but that'd be fatal in a battle against Gastrea.
ガストレアとの戦いでは致命的だ
Rather than increasing your defense,
防御力を上げるより
その分 身軽にして
it's better to make yourself
lighter to increase your speed.
スピード維持したほうが
合理的だろ？
I see...
なるほど
じゃあ 軽装なヤツがいいのだな
So it's better to pick people with light gear.
Let's see...
うんと～
I found them!
（延珠）見つけた！
（蓮太郎）おっ
I shall scout them!
スカウトしてくる！
Whoa, hey, wait a minute!
（蓮太郎）
わっ ちょっと待てって！
（延珠）ハァー
意外と見つからないものだな
They're harder to find than I expected.
Well, most of them are already
in other adjuvants...
すでに ほかのアジュバントに
入ってるヤツらが大半だからな
Let's head back for today.
今日は戻るか
Indeed...
そうだな
（男性の悲鳴）
（２人）あっ
Don't look, Enju!
（蓮太郎）見るな 延珠
（延珠）うっ…
Apparently a civil officer did it.
（民警）やったのは 民警らしいぞ
What a fool.
（民警）バカなヤツめ！
実力の違いも分からねえで
He had no idea they were
on a totally different level.
Rentaro!
（延珠）蓮太郎！
That's an impressive cut...
見事な切り口だ
Who could have...
一体 誰が…
It's a fight!
What the hell?
（民警）ケンカだ！
（民警）おい なんだよ！
Let's go!
Let's go, Rentaro.
行こう 蓮太郎
あれをやったヤツかもしれないぞ
It may be the one who killed them.
Right.
ああ
（延珠）ああ…
（蓮太郎）あっ
あっ
That's...
あれは… 彰磨兄？
Shoma-nii!
Don't you know who I am?
（ブリック）
俺様が誰だか知ってんのか？
The death row fugitive
wanted for robbery and murder,
強盗と殺人で死刑判決になっている
お尋ね者
Brick Nigel!
ブリック･ナイゲルたあ 俺のことよ
I never said you were weak.
（薙沢彰磨）
別に お前が弱いとは言ってない
Then why won't you drink my alcohol?
（ブリック）じゃあ なんで
俺の酒が飲めねえってんだ！
I'm not obligated to have you buy me a drink.
お前におごってもらう義理はない
What?!
何？
（民警たちのどよめき）
Why hasn't anyone realized it?
どうして 誰も気づかないのだ？
This match... They are clearly
on completely different levels.
この勝負
実力が違いすぎるであろう
You really shouldn't.
やめておけ
栄光も 矜持(きょうじ)もない戦いだ
A battle without honor or dignity
is rather boring, whether you win or lose.
勝っても負けても つまらんぞ
Shut up!
うるせー！
（少女）はーっ！
キャー！
（ブリック）うおー！
（ブリック）ぐっ あああ…
（歓声）
Amazing! That was amazing, Rentaro!
すごい！
すごいぞ 蓮太郎！
Rentaro?
あ… 蓮太郎？
That move... was Sandatama Kirin, right?
（蓮太郎）
さっきの技 三蛇玉麒麟(さんだたまきりん)だろ？
Your skills haven't waned a bit, Shoma-nii.
ちっとも衰えてねえな 彰磨兄
It's been a while, Satomi.
久しぶりだな 里見
I've been hearing about
your recent accomplishments.
お前の活躍
風のウワサに聞いている
Do you know him, Rentaro?
んー 知り合いなのか？ 蓮太郎
Let me introduce you, Enju.
紹介するよ 延珠
Rank eight in the Tendo Style
Martial Arts, Nagisawa Shoma.
天童式戦闘術８段 薙沢彰磨
He's my senior practitioner in the Tendo Style.
天童流の俺の兄弟子だ
Ever since I heard that
you defeated a Scorpion,
（彰磨）お前がスコーピオンを
倒したウワサを聞いてから―
I've been thinking about fighting alongside you.
ずっと いつか一緒に戦うことを
考えていた
Though I am unworthy,
不肖の身なれど
天童式戦闘術８段の力
allow me to join you in
your scheme with my power
as a rank eight in the
Tendo Style Martial Arts.
お前の悪だくみに 俺もまぜてくれ
That would be reassuring.
心強いよ
But why are you a civil officer, Shoma-nii?
でも 彰磨兄
なんで 民警なんかやってんだ？
Why did you up and leave the dojo so suddenly?
なんで 突然
道場 辞めちまったんだよ
I wasn't cut out for it.
俺は器じゃなかった
それだけだ
That's all.
Hey... can I ask you one other thing?
あのさ もう１つ聞いていいか？
The pair that was killed on the train tracks...
（彰磨）ん？
線路で殺されていたペアの死体は
彰磨兄たちの仕業か？
Did you guys do that?
What are you talking about?
なんのことだ？
Never mind, it's nothing.
いや なんでもない
Hey!
（玉樹）おーい！
We brought it!
持ってきたぜ
We're back!
（弓月）たっだいまー！
Nagisawa Shoma. Pleasure to work with you.
（彰磨）薙沢彰磨だ
よろしく頼む
I'm F-Fuse...
（布施(ふせ) 翠(みどり)）ふ… 布施
布施 翠といいまっしゅ
Fuse Midori.
I'm a Model Cat Initiator.
モデル･キャットの
イニシエーターです
（延珠･弓月）おおー！
M-My specialty is smell fortune-telling.
と… 特技は匂い占いです
Can you use magic?
お主 魔法は使えないのか？
M-Magic?
（翠）ま… 魔法!?
Well, you're wearing a witch's hat.
だって 魔女みたいな帽子
かぶってるではないか
Midori,
あっ
翠 仲間に隠し事はするな
you don't have to hide
anything among friends.
（延珠･弓月）おっ
おおー！
Is this even possible, Rentaro?
こんなことあるのか？ 蓮太郎
Yeah. I've heard of cases
where the animal factors
ああ　ガストレアウイルスに
含まれる動物因子が―
in the Gastrea virus strongly
affect the body of the host.
体に強く作用するケースも
あるって聞く
All right! Now we've got six!
しゃー！ これで６人！
That means our adjuvant is complete.
俺っちたちのアジュバントが
完成したってわけだ
Wait.
待て
Satomi, do you really
want to go with just six?
里見 お前は
このまま６人でいきたいのか？
Well... I'd like to have five pairs,
俺は 俺たちを含めて５組
10人欲しいと思ってる
so ten of us, if possible.
Do we really need that many?
（延珠）そんなに必要なのか？
I think the maximum number
of people I can direct,
俺がまとめきれる人数の限界と
as well as the number we'd
need to cover our blind spots,
パーティーの死角を
なくそうとしたときの
構成人数の折り合うのが
is right around that number.
俺は ちょうど
その辺だと思ってるんだ
Huh... So two other pairs...
はーん　あと２組ね
Just one more.
（木更）あと１組よ
（一同）あっ
Kisara-san?
（玉樹）おおー！
（蓮太郎）木更さん
Tendo Style swordsman
and Promoter, Tendo Kisara.
（木更）天童流剣士
プロモーター 天童木更
Mechanized soldier of the
"Next" program and Initiator,
“NEXT”の強化狙撃兵
イニシエーター
Tina Sprout.
ティナ･スプラウト
（ティナ）えっ？
The two of us
以上２名
have arrived unannounced to
join Satomi Rentaro's adjuvant.
里見蓮太郎のアジュバントに
加えていただきたく
ここに推参しました
Hold on a second!
ちょっと待て
ティナは序列剥奪処分中じゃ…
Tina's rank is currently revoked.
I personally had Seitenshi-sama withdraw that.
それなら
聖天子様に直接 掛け合って
取り消してもらったわ
We're at a critical point where
the Tokyo Area being destroyed.
今は 東京エリア消滅の
瀬戸際だからね
Then...
それじゃ…
I just finished registering us.
登録は さっき済ませたわ
Our rank starts at 9,200.
私とティナちゃんの序列は
9200番からスタートよ
Though I'm sure our actual ability
is a little higher than that.
でも 実力のほうは
もうちょっと上のはずよ
I'd say it's a bit more than "a little higher."
もうちょっとどころで済むかよ
（木更）ウフフ…
It's been a while, Kisara.
久しいな 木更
えっ？
What?! You're kidding! Shoma-kun?!
ええっ？
ウソ 彰磨くん!?
Was I rude to address a senior
practitioner by her first name?
姉弟子に呼び捨てはマズいか？
I don't mind.
We've known each other forever.
いいわよ
昔からの仲なんだから
More importantly, where have
you been all this time?
そんなことより
今まで どこにいたの？
More importantly, come here a sec!
そんなことより ちょっと来い！
Wait, Satomi-kun!
（木更）
ちょ… ちょっと 里見くん？
She's a goddess...
（玉樹）女神だ
（弓月）ん？
I have a goddess...
俺っちの女神がいる！
Bro, are you all right in the head?
兄貴
頭 大丈夫？
Think about your health for a minute!
少しは 自分の体のこと考えろよ！
I already went for my dialysis today.
透析治療なら
今日は もう行ってきたわ
You will allow me to join your adjuvant!
私もアジュバントに入れること
これは社長命令よ！
That is your president's order!
Like I could listen to that ord—
そんな命令 聞けるわけ…
Onii-san...
（ティナ）お兄さん
（蓮太郎）あっ
Do you not want me to be on your team?
私が仲間になるの イヤですか？
（蓮太郎）うっ うう…
Oh, damn it!
あー ったく！
Pardon.
（自衛官）失礼！
Commander Gado has ordered
all civil officers to gather
全ての民警は １９３０時に―
前線司令部前に集まるよう
我堂(がどう)団長から 招集がかかりました
in front of headquarters at 1930 hours.
Thank you all for coming.
（我堂長政(ながまさ)）よくぞ集まってくれた
I am your commander, Gado Nagamasa.
私は 団長を務める我堂長政だ
You have all been chosen
to save the Tokyo Area.
諸君らは 東京エリアを救う
選ばれし者たちだ
I am proud to be able to
fight alongside you all.
共に戦えることを 私は誇りに思う
That's...
あれが…
Rank 275, Gado Nagamasa.
序列275位 我堂長政
The Tokyo Area is currently in terrible danger.
（長政）今 東京エリアは
未曽有の危機にある
The Gastrea are a fearsome enemy,
ガストレアは 恐るべき敵だが―
but if anyone is able to defeat them, it is us!
ヤツらを覆すことのできる者は
我々を置いて ほかにない！
Kill them!
ヤツらを殺せー！
It is your duty to kill as many as possible
of the loathsome Gastrea
我々の家族を 恋人を殺した
憎きガストレアを―
that killed our families and those we loved!
１匹でも多く殺すことが
諸君らの責務である
It is the victors who have created
our history up until now.
今日(こんにち)の歴史は
勝者こそが創ってきたのだ
We will win and be the writers of history!
我々は勝利して
歴史の創始者となるのだ
We shall kill them all!
ヤツらを殺すぞー！
Yeah!
（一同）うおー！
That's a pretty effective speech for a
血の気の多い民警連中には
効果てきめんなご演説だな
bunch of hot-blooded civil officers.
Indeed. He's just as I heard.
ああ
ウワサどおりの切れ者らしい
Currently, the Gastrea army and the JASDF
現在 32号モノリスを挟んで―
are glaring at each other from
either side of Monolith 32.
ガストレア軍団と自衛隊が
にらみ合っている
As soon as the battle begins,
戦闘が始まれば
我々は 自衛隊の要請に従い―
we shall send in support squads
according to the request of the JASDF.
支援部隊を送る！
So we don't get any action
until they actually call on us.
ハッ
要するに俺っちたちは
お呼びがかかるまで
出番なしってことか
Are there any questions?
質問がある者は？
ん？
Huh? Wait, Satomi-kun...
えっ？
ちょっと 里見くん？
You're rather young. Who might you be?
（長政）若いな 何者だ
Rank 300, Satomi Rentaro.
序列300位 里見蓮太郎
（長政）ん？
Ah, so you're...
ほう 君が…
Considering we're here as
the JASDF's rear guard,
自衛隊の後詰めっていうわりには
the civil officer forces are
pretty distant from the JASDF.
民警軍団と自衛隊の間が
離れすぎてる
Why is that?
どういうわけだ？
We have only been
（長政）我々は ただ
後方にて陣を設け待機せよと―
ordered to create our
encampment and be on standby.
命令されただけだ
Then why don't we move
our encampment closer?
じゃあ いっそ
もっと陣を下げたらどうだ？
There's a place near the
Flames of Revolution monument
“回帰の炎”の記念碑辺りなら
where we could effectively hide
ourselves for guerrilla warfare.
ゲリラ戦に有利な
身を隠せる場所がある
Then we won't be able to
immediately respond to
それでは 自衛隊の支援要請に
迅速に応えられない
the JASDF's call for aid.
Do you honestly think that call will come?
そんなもの
本当に来ると思ってんのか？
（長政）ん…
A one and a two...
（延珠･弓月）いっせーのーで！
No!
にゃー！
Wh-What are you doing?!
な… 何するんですか？
We wanted to see if you had a tail, as well.
（延珠）尻尾も付いてるか
確かめようと思って
I do not!
（翠）付いてませーん！
That really scared me.
もう ビックリしたわよ
Thankfully, the meeting ended before
anything drastic happened, but...
何事もなく解散になったから
よかったものの
Do you just feel the need to
go after anyone in power?
里見くんは 偉い人見ると
突っかからずにいられないの？
I just wanted our doubts addressed.
疑問を解消しようとしただけだろ
More importantly, are you really
planning on fighting with us?
それより 本当に
俺たちと一緒に戦うつもりなのか？
Jeez... Are you still going on about that?
もう まだ言ってるの？
Kisara-san...
木更さん
If something were to happen to you, I...
あんたに もしものことがあったら
俺は…
Why can't you realize I feel the same?
どうして 私も同じだって
気づかないの？
あ… えっ？
I don't want to just sit there and pray
私だって 里見くんが
危ない目に遭ってるとき
while you're putting yourself
in danger, Satomi-kun!
ただ お祈りしてるしかないなんて
イヤよ そんなの！
Please, Satomi-kun.
お願い 里見くん
If I end up getting in the way,
you're welcome to leave me behind.
足手まといになるようなら
切り捨てていってかまわないから
I won't let that happen.
そんなこと させねえよ
I'll protect you, Kisara-san.
木更さんは 俺が守る
So don't worry.
だから 心配すんな
あ… もう おバカ
Jeez... You idiot...
あっ
K-Kisara-san, I...
き… 木更さん 俺…
Huh?
えっ？
I...
俺…
Ahem.
（せきばらい）
Whoa!
（２人）うわっ！
You bastard!
What are you doing to my goddess?!
（玉樹）てめえ 俺っちの女神に！
（蓮太郎）はあ？
Wha?
Kisara, you seduced Rentaro
by letting him grope
（延珠）木更！
また デカパイつかませて―
your huge boobs again, didn't you?
蓮太郎を誘惑したな！
I-I didn't let anyone grope anything!
（木更）つ… つかませてないわ！
That's disgusting.
That didn't happen!
（ティナ）不潔です
（蓮太郎）そんなわけねえだろ！
Uh, it might be a little weird
to reintroduce ourselves, but...
（蓮太郎）あー
改めて自己紹介ってのも
変な感じだけど
I'm Satomi Rentaro.
里見蓮太郎だ
Aihara Enju!
藍原延珠
Tendo Kisara!
天童木更
Tina Sprout.
ティナ･スプラウト
Katagiri Tamaki.
片桐玉樹
Katagiri Yuzuki!
片桐弓月
Nagisawa Shoma.
薙沢彰磨
I'm F-Fuse Midori.
ふ… 布施 翠です
Thank you all for helping me out.
（蓮太郎）みんな
俺なんかのために
力を貸してくれて ありがとう
For these three days between the destruction
and reconstruction of the Monolith,
モノリス崩壊から
代替えモノリス到着までの３日
let's see this fight through together!
力を合わせて戦い抜こう！
Jeez, you're so dramatic.
もう 大げさなんだから
My life is yours, Onii-san.
私の命は お兄さんのものです
Rentaro,
蓮太郎 俺っちが貸した力
おろそかに使うんじゃねえぞ！
you better not squander the
power I'm lending you!
Rentaro, since our team is together,
we need to have a cheer.
（延珠）蓮太郎！
（蓮太郎）うおっ
仲間がそろったから
エイエイオーだ！
What the hell?
なんだ それ
The Tenchu Girls always do a cheer!
天誅(てんちゅう)ガールズが
いつもやる掛け声だ
We're all with you!
Of course we're going to win!
妾たちがついているのだ！
絶対 勝てるに決まっている！
Yeah...
ああ
All right, let's do this!
じゃあ みんな いくぞ！
エイエイ…
（一同）オー！
One more time!
（延珠）もう１回！
（一同）エイエイオー！
♪～
～♪
#10 Tokyo Area Defensive Battle
I realized that this happiness will end one day...
（木更）いつか この幸せに―
終わりがくるんだって気づいたら…
（延珠）放せー！
Let go of me!
Just who are we protecting?
（蓮太郎）
俺たちは 誰を守ってるんだ？
Who are we supposed to fight for?!
誰のために戦えばいい
なんのために！
For what?!